reserveout.com 2019-05-04

# Privacy

###  Privacy policy 

RESERVEOUT LTD, owner and operator of [www.reserveout.com](http://www.reserveout.com/) ("reserveout"), is committed to safeguarding your privacy. This Privacy Policy describes Reserveout's policies and procedures on the collection, use and disclosure of the information collected through Reserveout's websites, which include [www.reserveout.com](http://www.reserveout.com/) and Reserveout mobile applications (hereinafter referred to collectively as the "Reserveout Network") and "User" or "you" refers to you. 

#####  About the Reserveout network: 

The Reserveout Network, which includes, but is not limited to,restaurants, spas, clubs and various entertainment Venues (the Venues) listed on the Reserveout Network have each adopted Reserveout's proprietary electronic reservation system (the Reserveout Terminal). The Reserveout Network interacts with the Venues in the Reserveout Terminal to find available reservations, to secure, change or cancel online reservations, and to confirm that reservations were honored. While an individual Venue's availability is accessible to the Reserveout Network to perform these functions, other User information that may be stored by that Venue (for example, reminders about User preferences) is not accessible to the Reserveout Network. Similarly, the Reserveout Network passes pertinent information to the Reserveout Terminal and therefore to individual Venues as required to secure or cancel online reservations. Individual Venues, however, cannot access any information from the Reserveout Network. In some instances a Venue may operate its own website and collect a myriad of User information directly as part of the online reservation process. In those cases, only the information passed directly to the Reserveout Network to complete the transaction is stored by the Reserveout Network (e.g. User name and phone number).   
This document describes how the Reserveout Network User information is collected, stored, used and, in specific instances, shared with Venues via their Reserveout Terminal. 

There are two ways you can make reservations online using the Reserveout Network. 

######  Unregistered Users: 

As an Unregistered User, you will be asked to provide a name and a telephone number in order to complete the reservation, as you usually would be when making a reservation over the phone. In addition, you will be asked to provide an email address to which Reserveout will send automated service messages pertaining to your reservation. Reserveout will use this email address for no other purpose unless you have consented to receive marketing communications from either Reserveout or from Venues at which you've made online reservations. Unregistered Users cannot save their information and preferences for future visits. 

######  Signed up Users: 

If you choose to sign up with Reserveout (become a Registered User) in order to take advantage of certain Reserveout benefits, you will be asked to provide a name, a telephone number, an email address, and a password of your choice. You may choose not to receive marketing communications from Reserveout or from the Venue at which you've made an online reservation, other than automated service messages pertaining to your reservation. 

##### What personal information do we collect from the people that use our service? :

  1. Your name, email ID, and, or mobile number at the time of you registering on our mobile app
  2. Your mobile device location when you use our mobile app (specific location if youâve enabled GPS, or general geographic location based on your internet connection service provider)
  3. General information about your device like type of device, operating system, and version
  4. Our mobile app optionally offers connection with your social media accounts (only Facebook currently). We collect the basic information provided by these social media accounts while connecting if user opts to do so
  5. Your activities on the app like your searches, results you selected, screens you visited, calls you placed to merchants through our app, content you shared on social media (Facebook, Twitter, etc.) through the app

#####  What information is accessible to Venues: 

When you make a reservation at a Venue using the Reserveout Network, your name, telephone number, and sometimes your email are provided to that Venue, just as would occur if you were making a reservation over the phone.   
Reserveout will only share the information specified above with the Venue at which you have made reservations using the Reserveout Network. Venues cannot use their Reserveout Terminal to access information pertaining to Users or User's histories from other Venues, with the exception that Venues under the same corporate ownership may elect to share User information between Venue properties. 

#####  Email from Reserveout: 

Email from Reserveout: 

#####  Email from Venues: 

You may consent to receive marketing communications from the Venue at which you've made a reservation. Reserveout plays no role in the content, frequency, timing or unsubscription process of any Venue's marketing communications. If you would like to unsubscribe from a Venue's marketing communications, please contact the appropriate Venue directly. 

##### Social Media:

You can choose to access certain third party social media web sites and services through the Reserveout Network. When you do so, you are sharing information with those sites, and the information you share will be governed by their privacy policies. You can modify your privacy settings with those third parties directly. Reserveout does not control the privacy policies of such third parties and assumes no responsibility or liability for the actions of such third parties. 

##### Purposes of use of your personal information:

Reserveout may use your personal information for the following purposes: 

  1. to secure your reservation at the Reserveout Venue you've selected, by providing your name and contact phone number to that Venue
  2. to provide you with other products and services of the Reserveout Network
  3. to provide you with information about the services of the Reserveout Network
  4. to provide services which Registered Users are entitled to under applicable terms and conditions
  5. to produce aggregate statistical data for the improvement of services offered by the Reserveout Network, or for any other purposes related to those above
  6. to personalize your experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested 
  7. to securely connect you with your friends to message within the network
  8. to improve our service in order to better serve you
  9. to allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests
  10. To send periodic emails and push notifications regarding content that we feel might interest you

Viewing your profile and changing your personal information: Once a Registered User logs on to the Reserveout Network, that User can view his or her personal information stored by Reserveout by clicking on the "Profile" link at the top of the page. In addition to being able to view your recent Reserveout reservation history every User may also view and change the following personal information: name, email address, password, phone number, birthday (if it has been provided by the User), address (if it has been provided by the User), special requests that should be forwarded to Venues when making reservations (if they have been provided by the User), and whether that User would like to receive marketing communications from Reserveout. A User may also be eligible to provide and share Venue notes and feedback for some past reservations that have been honored. The User at any time may contact Reserveout to request that all personal information be deactivated.

##### How Reserveout uses your personal information:

Reserveout will never sell, rent, loan or otherwise distribute any of your personal information (including but not limited to your name, email address, phone number or any other identifiable information about you) to any third party without your prior expressed written consent, although Reserveout will pass certain information on to Venues at which you make reservations as described above. Notwithstanding anything to the contrary in this privacy policy, Reserveout may be required to disclose User and personal information in response to inquiries by formal law enforcement under the authority of Jordanian privacy laws and regulations. 

##### How Venues may use your personal information:

Venues in the Reserveout Network primarily use User information provided through the Reserveout Network to secure the desired reservations.   
Reserveout Venues want to provide you with the best possible service so that you will visit them again. One way Venues can distinguish themselves is by recognizing returning Users and recalling their special preferences. For this reason, a restaurant may use its Reserveout Terminal to take note of your special requests, allergies, special occasions or other pertinent information that will help the Venue serve you better during your next visit.   
The Venues within Reserveout's network are separate businesses from Reserveout. Therefore Reserveout will not be responsible if these Venues fail to comply with respect to your information. Any complaints or inquiries regarding use of your information by an Reserveout Venue, or marketing communications from an Reserveout Venue, should be addressed directly to the Venue in question.   
Venues within the Reserveout Network may also have their own websites. Reserveout is not responsible for how these Venues may collect your personal information through their own websites. Please contact the appropriate Venue regarding its website's privacy policy (if applicable) and how it will access or use your personal information. 

##### How Reserveout protects your registration information:

Reserveout stores all of your personal information on a secure server. Reserveout employs a staff that regularly maintains the security of all personal information stored, and that continually monitors and implements changes and improvements that become available in the electronic data security industry. 

##### Third party links & disclosure:

Reserveout use third party services like CleverTap, Fabric, Adjust and Branch to which we disclose certain personally identifiable information you provide us such as name, email, mobile phone number and device information. 

##### Cookies and Interest-Based Advertising Policy:

Some of the advertisements you see on the Site are selected and delivered by third parties, such as ad networks, advertising agencies, advertisers, and audience segment providers. These third parties may collect information about you and your online activities, either on the Site or on other websites, through cookies, web beacons, and other technologies in an effort to understand your interests and deliver to you advertisements that are tailored to your interests. Please remember that we do not have access to, or control over, the information these third parties may collect. The information practices of these third parties are not covered by this privacy policy. 

##### Changes to Reserveout's privacy policy:

The Website Policies and Terms & Conditions may be changed or updated occasionally to meet the requirements and standards. Therefore the CustomersÃ¢ÂÂ are encouraged to frequently visit these sections in order to be updated about the changes on the website. Modifications will be effective on the day they are posted. 

Reserveout will never make changes to its privacy policy that violate any applicable privacy laws or commercial privacy standards. 

All credit/debit cards details and personally identifiable information will NOT be stored, sold, shared, rented or leased to any third parties. 

##### Disclosure, correction, suspension of use of personal information:

If you wish to have Reserveout disclose to you the personal information held by Reserveout and the means through which Reserveout obtained such information, or if you desire the information's correction, suspension of use, or to be informed of the purpose of use by Reserveout, please contact Reserveout. (Contact information is provided in the "Contacting Reserveout " section below.) Upon receiving the request, Reserveout shall meet such request pursuant to the provisions of each applicable privacy regulation after it confirms that such request has been made by you personally. 

##### Contacting Reserveout:

For questions regarding how to access and change your personal information visit [www.reserveout.com](http://www.reserveout.com/) or contact customer support at [support@reserveout.com](mailto:support@reserveout.com)
